Local 1199 Oral History Project 5680 OH
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Oral History Project
1975-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Employees Union (RWDSU)
National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (NUHHCE)
Local 1199
Greenberg, Brian
Fink, Leon
5680 OH
57.39 cubic feet
55.2 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genres).
The unedited oral history interviews of the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees discuss the evolution of the Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union drugstore local (known as Local 1199 and District 1199), representing pharmacists and drug clerks in New York City, into an international union of professional and non-professional workers in voluntary and non-profit health institutions, including hospitals, clinics and nursing homes, as well as drug stores.
6855757
Biographical / Historical
Between 1933 and 1957, 1199 functioned as a drugstore local with its membership growing to 5,000 workers employed in independent and chain drugstores throughout the New York metropolitan area. With its success in organizing workers in Montefiore Hospital in New York City, the union began a massive campaign to organize workers in voluntary and non-profit hospitals in the New York area, a large proportion of whom were black or Hispanic. In 1973, the national union was established with locals in other states, including Pennsylvania, Maryland, South and North Carolina, Connecticut, New Jersey, and Massachusetts. The union combined organizing efforts with civil rights organizations, in an effort to achieve mutual political goals. Throughout the period discussed in these interviews, the union was led by Leon Davis (president, Local 1199 and the National Union) whose administration guided the union's political and social activities. The unedited oral history interviews of the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees discuss the evolution of the Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union drugstore local, representing pharmacists and drug clerks in New York City (known as Local 1199 and District 1199) into an international union of non-professional and professional workers in voluntary and non-profit health institutions, including hospitals, clinics and nursing homes, as well as drugstores.
Scope and Contents
Interviews with union leaders, delegates, and members include Ernestine Bowen, Thelma Bowles, Grace Glassberg, Nellie Morris, Mildren Reeves, Mary Riley, Betty Rosoff, Doris Turner, Kay Tillow, Sarah Goldstein, Diane Bianculli, Hilda Joquin, Ida Cameron, and other women and men.
Consists of one hundred and fifty hours (eighty-three transcriptions) of interviews relating to the National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees.
These interviews were begun in 1975 as a pilot study funded by the union and initially focused on the development of work-related conflict and union organization in Montefiore Hospital, Bronx, New York. The investigators, Brian Greenberg and Leon Fink, later extended their analysis of Montefiore to cover the major events that occurred in the development of 1199 through 1973. The respondents in this collection of interviews include officers and staff of 1199; rank and file membership; delegates and organizers; individuals involved with the Charleston, South Carolina hospital strike (1969); administrators of various New York City hospitals; and prominent labor, civil rights and health care industry figures.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 16, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; African-Americans -- Civil rights -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African-Americans -- Civil rights -- United States; African-Americans -- Suffrage -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hospitals -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hospitals -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Law and legislation -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Municipal employees -- New York (State); Charleston (S.C.) -- Race relations; Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- Law and legislation -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- Pennsylvania; Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Collective bargaining -- Hospitals -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Law and legislation -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Employee attitudes -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Employee attitudes -- Hospitals -- United States; Employee fringe benefits -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Dismissal of -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Dismissal of -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Hospitals -- Employees -- Training of -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Training of -- United States; Grievance procedures -- Drug trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Grievance procedures -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospital -- Employees -- Political activity -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Hospitals -- Industrial relations -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Industrial relations -- United States; Hospitals -- Personnel management -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston -- Personnel management; Hours of labor -- Drug trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Hours of labor -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Hours of labor -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Disability insurance -- Hospitals -- Employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Job descriptions -- New York (State) -- New York; Nurses -- Job descriptions -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Job satisfaction -- New York (State) -- New York; Job security -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Working class -- Education -- New York (State); Labor discipline -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor disputes -- Hospitals -- United States; Labor productivity -- Drug trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor turnover -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor turnover -- Hospitals -- United States; Labor violence -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor-management cooperation -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Layoffs -- Drug trade -- United States; Layoffs -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Hospitals -- New York (State); Misconduct -- Drug trade -- New York (State) -- New York; National health insurance -- United States; Race relations -- New York (State) -- New York; Nurses -- In-service training -- New York (State) -- New York; Nurses -- Salaries, etc. -- New York (State) -- New York; Occupations and race -- Drugstores -- New York (State) -- New York; Occupations and race -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Occupations and race -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Open and closed shop -- Hospitals -- United States; Hospitals -- Employees -- Pensions -- New York (State) -- New York; Position classification -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Promotions -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Public relations -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Public relations -- United States; Rank and file participation -- Drug trade employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Rank and file participation -- New York (State) -- New York; Rank and file participation; Hospitals -- Employees -- Recruiting -- New York (State) -- New York; Seniority, Employee -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Social security -- Law and legislation -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Drug trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Strikes and lockouts -- Drug trade -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Strikes and lockouts -- Hospitals -- Pennsylvania; Strikes and lockouts -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Strikes and lockouts -- Hospitals -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Strikes and lockouts -- Law and legislation -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- New York (State) -- State supervision; Strikes and lockouts -- Sanitation workers -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Strikes and lockouts -- State supervision -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Hospitals -- Employees -- Supervision -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Cultural activity -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor union democracy; Union dues -- New York (State) -- New York; Union dues -- United States; Union dues; Labor unions -- Officials and employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Officials and employees -- United States; Labor unions -- Recognition -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor union structure -- United States; Agricultural laborers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Pharmaceutical industry -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Pharmaceutical industry -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Drugstore employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Maryland -- Baltimore; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Michigan -- Detroit; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New Jersey; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania; Hospitals -- Employees -- Labor unions -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Labor unions -- Maryland -- Baltimore; Labor unions -- Michigan -- Detroit; Labor unions, Black -- Membership -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Elections -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Jurisdictional disputes -- New York (State) -- New York; Minority labor union members -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Puerto Rican membership -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Social aspects -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- Organizing -- New York (State); Nurses -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Nurses -- Labor unions -- United States; Labor unions, Black -- Membership -- Pennsylvania; Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Minority membership; Labor unions -- Organizing -- Pennsylvania; Pharmacists -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Porters -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Taxicab drivers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Labor unions, Black -- Membership -- United States; Labor unions -- United States -- Corrupt practices; Labor unions -- United States -- Minority membership; Labor unions -- United States -- Recognition; Labor unions -- United States -- Social action; White collar workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; White collar workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Unemployment -- Drug trade -- United States; Unfair labor practices -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Wages -- Pharmaceutical industry employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Salaries, etc. -- New York (State) -- New York; Hospitals -- Employees -- Salaries, etc. -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Hospitals -- Employees -- Salaries, etc. -- United States; Wages -- Law and legislation -- United States; Minimum wage -- Law and legislation -- United States; Work assignments -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Pharmaceutical industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Workers' education -- Hospitals -- Employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Working conditions -- Drugstores -- New York (State) -- New York; Working conditions -- Hospitals -- New York (State) -- New York; Working conditions -- Hospitals -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Working conditions -- Hospitals -- United States; World War, 1939-1945 -- African-Americans; United States -- Race relations; Employee rules; Nurses -- Pensions -- New York (State) -- New York; Absenteeism (Labor); Solidarity; Labor unions -- United States; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963; Abernathy, Ralph. (Ralph David). 1926-; Al-Amin, Jamil, 1943-; Anderson, Billy; Arana, Gloria; Ayash, Eddie; Badillo, Herman, 1929-2014; Balancia, Charles.; Barker, Sylvia; Barkum, Marie; Beame, Abraham D. (Abraham David), 1906-2001; Begel, Jack; Belchman, Arnold; Berenger, Hiram; Bianculli, Diane; Bowen, Ernestine; Bowles, Thelma; Boykin, Jim; Bragg, Edward; Brand, Rose; Broomer, Sy; Brown, Joseph; Bryant, Jim; Burgess, Clifton; Burke, Bob; Buttenwieser, Benjamin; Buttenwieser, Helen; Cameron, Ida; Carbonnel, Ricky; Carlino, Anthony; Carlino, Joseph; Carmichael, Stokely, 1941-1998; Cherkasky, Martin; Clark, Evans, 1888-1970; Clark, Septima Poinsette, 1898-1987; Coffee, Edward; Connorton, John; Copper, Gouvenir; Corbett, Raymond; Corbin, Saul; Cordero, Salvadore, 1876-1951; Cosby, Cassie; Cruz, Emerito; Danielli, Andrew; David, Aberdeen; Davis, Leon, 1907-; DeMarco, Edward; Downs, Ken; Dubin, Marshall; Ehrlichman, John; Epstein, Harry; Farmer, James, 1920-1999; Feinberg, I. Robert (Irving Robert), 1912-1975; Felix, Harold; Ferrara, Claude; Field, Felix; Fitzpatrick, James Henry, 1922-; Foner, Moe, 1915-; Fox, Larry; Freedman, Jesse; Glassberg, Grace; Godoff, Elliott.; Godoff, Lillian; Goffshagen, Irving; Goldman, Milton; Goldstein, Sarah; Gorelick, Howard; Grant, Henry, Rev.; Greenberg, Max; Greenberg, Brian; Haldeman, H. R. (Harry R.), 1926-1993; Harrison, Mae; Healey, James H., 1920-; Heldeman, Robert; Herbst, Frankie; Hodara, Morris; Hoffa, James R. (James Riddle), 1913-; Hurt, Frank D.; Jenkins, Essau; Joaquin, Hilda; Kamenkowitz, Phil; Katz, Bernie; Katz, Morris; Kaufman, David; Kay, Edward; Kempton, Murray, 1917-1997; Kennedy, Edward M. q (Edward Moore), 1932-2009; Kennedy, Ethel, 1928-; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968; Kilbourne, Thomas; King, Coretta Scott, 1927-2006; King, Martin Luther, 1899-1984; King, Telbert; Kirchway, Fieda; Kirschner, Abe; Kosloski, Al; La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947; Landsberg, Arthur; Lerner, Oscar; Levinson, Stanley; Lewis, Bill B.; Lichtenstein, Howard; Lindsay, John V. (John Vliet); Livingston, David; Lovestone, Jay; Malave, Ramon; McCain, Robert; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Metzger, Norman, 1924-; Michaelson, Bill; Mitchell, Ted; Molosky, Sollie; Mondale, Walter F., 1928-; Monserrat, Joseph; Morris, Nellie; Moultries, Mary; Moynihan, Daniel P. (Daniel Patrick), 1927-2003; Muehlenkamp, Robert; Nicholas, Henry; Olson, Jesse; O'Neil, Jonnie; Oritz, Arquilla; Otley, Peter; Pagan, Julio; Paley, Hank; Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr., 1908-1972; Provasti, Leo; Quill, Mike; Ramirez, Armando; Randolph, A. Philip (Asa Philip), 1889-1979; Raskin, A. H.
6855757
- Raskin, A. H.: interview 51 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Pagan, Julio: interview 50 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  2nd tape impossible to transcribe
- Ortiz, Arquilla: interview 49 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Nicholas, H.: interview 48 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  2nd interview
- Nicholas, Henry: interview 48 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Muehlen Kamp, Robert: interview 47 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Moultries: interview 46 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Morris, Nellie: interview 45 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Mitchell, Ted (II): interview 44 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Mitchell, Ted (I): interview 43 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Michaelson, Bill: interview 42 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Metzger, Norman: interview 41 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Malave: interview 40 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Kosloski, Al: interview 39 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Kay, Eddie: interview 38 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Kaufman, O.: interview 37 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Kamenkowitz, Phil: interview 36 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lichtenstein, Howard: interview 35 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Joquin, Hilda: interview 34 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hodara, Morris: interview 33 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Grant: interview 32 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Goldstein, Sarah: interview 31 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Godoff, L.: interview 30 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Glassberg, Grace: interview 29 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Foner, Moe: interview 28 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Foner, Moe: interview 27 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Foner, Moe: interview 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Foner, Moe: interview 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fitzpatrick, James: interview 24 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ferrara, Claude: interview 23 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Duffy, Thomas (Rev.: interview 22 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Dubin, Marshall: interview 21 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Downs, Ken: interview 20 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Davis, L.: interview 19 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Davis, L.: interview 18 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Davis, Leon: interview 17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Davis, Leon: interview 16 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Davis, Leon: interview 15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cruz, Emerito: interview 14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  only one side transcribed
- Cormack, J.: interview 13 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Cordero, Salvadore: interview 12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Cooper, Governor: interview 11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Connorton, John B.: interview 10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Cherkasky, Martin: interview 9 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Bryant, Jim: interview 8 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Balancia, Charles: interview 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Barkum, M.: interview 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Bennett, Isaiah: interview 3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bowens, E.: interview 4 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bowles, Thelma: interview 5 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Brand/Barker: interview 6 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Brown, Joseph: interview 7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Young: interview 75 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Works, L.: interview 74 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Wise, John E.: interview 73 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- White, Dave: interview 72 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Weingarten, Victor: interview 71 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Volk, Cornelius: interview 70 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- VanArsdale, Harry: interview 69 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Turner, Doris: interview 68 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  2 copies - 1 original and 1 photocopy
- Turner, Doris: interview 68 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Tompkins: interview 67 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Tillow, Kay: interview 66 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Taylor: interview 65 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Stern, Irving: interview 64 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Steinberg, Martin: interview 63 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Steinberg, Martin: interview 62 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Singletary, Clarence (Judge): interview 61 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Sheps, Cecil: interview 60 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Schmuckler, Sam: interview 59 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Saunders: interview 58 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Rustin, Bayard: interview 56 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Sanchez: interview 57 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Roth, Karl: interview 55 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rosoff, Betty: interview 54 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Riley, Mary: interview 53 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Reeves: interview 52 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Joseph Brown: 11/12/1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Side 1 #1
- Joseph Brown: 11/12/1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  tape 1/side 2
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Jim Bryant: 3/23/1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  side 1
- Jim Bryant: 3/23/1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  side 2
- G. Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- G. Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- G. Cooper: 12/14/1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  side 1 only -- box is EMPTY, leaving it with collection in case the tape shows up
- G. Cooper: 12/19/1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  tape 2/side 1
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  side 1 only
- Joseph Brown (Box 7, Folder 2)
  tape 2/side 1 only
- Thelma Bowles: 2/18/1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  tape 1/side 1
- Thelma Bowles: 12/3/1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Ernestine Bowen: 3/23/1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  tape 2/side 1 [side 2 was blank]
- Thelma Bowles: 2/18/1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Ernestine Bowen: 3/23/1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Ernestine Bowen 3/23/1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  tape 2/side 2
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Moe Foner: 4/1/1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Moe Foner 3: 12/23/1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  tape 3/side 1
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Claude Ferrara (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Claude Ferrara: 3/16/1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Claude Ferrara: 3/16/1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Ken Downs (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Ken Downs (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Ken Downs (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Ken Downs (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Sal Cordero: 12/15/1975 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Sal Cordero: 12/15/1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Moe Foner: 7/22/1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977a (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Moe Foner: 7/1/1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Moe Foner: 12/23/1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Moe Foner: 10/26/1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Moe Foner: 10/26/1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Grace Glassberg: 3/23/1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Grace Glassberg: 3/23/1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Morris Hodara (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Morris Hodara (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Hodara 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Hodara 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Ramon Malave (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Ramon Malave: 12/6/1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  side 1/tape 1
- Ramon Malave :12/6/1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Arguilla Ortiz: 7/11/1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Arguilla Ortiz: 7/11/1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Ted Mitchell: 9/28/1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Ted Mitchell: 9/28/1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Nellie Morris: 1/8/1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Nellie Morris: 1/8/1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Henry Nicholas (Box 12, Folder 9)
  tape 3/side 1 only
- Henry Nicholas: 1/11/1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Henry Nicholas (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Henry Nicholas (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/12/1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/12/1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Henry Nicholas: 4/12/1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Henry Nicholas: 10/14/1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Henry Nicholas: 10/14/1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Mildren Reeves (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Mildren Reeves (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Mildren Reeves (Box 14, Folder 1)
  tape 1/side 2 - complete
- Mildren Reeves (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Mary Riley: 7/6/1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Mary Riley: 7/6/1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Betty Rosoff: 12/8/1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Betty Rosoff: 12/8/1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Betty Rosoff: 12/8/1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Bayard Rustin: 6/20/1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Bayard Rustin: 6/20/1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Sam Schmuchler: 4/4/1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Sam Schmuchler: 4/4/1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Sam Schmuckler: 4/4/1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Irving Stern: 1/16/1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Irving Stern: 1/16/1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Doris Turner: 11/23/1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)